madeeha w. lamoreaux

3337 Pillsbury Ave S 224.715.6517 madeeha.lamoreaux@gmail.com

Multimedia Artist & Educator

b. UK, 1990

Summary

Collaborative and compassionate educator with broad technical expertise and a global perspective. Highly skilled written and verbal communicator with personal drive to develop thoughtful and engaging courses focused on emerging technology. Proven commitment to equity through research and revision of established courses with a focus on diversity and inclusion.

Education

| 2016 MFA | Media, Art, Design, and Technology |
|----------|------------------------------------|
| | E I NA I I I'I I NII |

Frank Mohr Institute, NL

2013 BA Creative Writing and Fine Art (+ Digital Design Minor)

Lake Forest College, USA

Experience

| 2021 - current | Adjunct Lecturer | MGAWD Program, Minneapolis College of Art and Design |
|----------------|------------------------------|--|
| 2017 - current | Adjunct Lecturer | Dept. of Art & Art History, Lake Forest College |
| 2017 - 19 | Full Stack Designer | Alysha & Co. |
| 2017 - 18 | Photo Retoucher | Classic Kids V Lab |
| 2017 – 17 | Graphic Design + Art [| irection Simply Wood Rings |
| 2014 | Shop Assistant | Asrai Garden |
| 2013 | Events Marketing Inte | rn Lillstreet Art Center |
| 2013 | Artist Studio Assistan | Tracy Marie Taylor |
| 2011-2013 | Full Stack Web Design | er Dept. of English, Lake Forest College |

Toolset

| Web + Graphic | HTML 5, CSS3, JavaScript, Adobe Illustrator, InDesign, Photoshop, |
|---------------|---|
| | Lightroom, Adobe XD, Figma |
| Mixed Reality | Blender, Autodesk Maya, Unity 3D, Spark AR |
| Production | Lasercutting, Basic Woodworking, 3D Print, 2D (Photo) Print |
| Programming | Arduino IDE, Python |